{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Advanced Systems Integration and Architecture",
    "Term": "Prefinals",
    "Title": "Enterprise Asset Management (EAM) Part 2",
    "LastModified": "20 November 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "05 Handout 1 - 2"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "Malfunctions and other requirements are gathered in ______.",
      "answer": "Notifications",
      "choices": [
        "Notifications",
        "Plant",
        "Storage Location",
        "Bill of Material"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It tells maintenance that something needs fixing by highlighting a breakdown that needs to be actioned quickly.",
      "answer": "Notifications",
      "choices": [
        "Notifications",
        "Announcement",
        "Maintanance",
        "Maintenance Plant"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It can be used to record works already carried out because a history needs to be maintained.",
      "answer": "Notifications",
      "choices": [
        "Notifications",
        "Announcement",
        "Maintanance",
        "Maintenance Plant"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following must a notification have?",
      "answer": "Technical object",
      "choices": [
        "Technical object",
        "Time Confirmation",
        "Technical Completion Confirmation",
        "Printing work instruction papers"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following must a notification have?",
      "answer": "Location data",
      "choices": [
        "Location data",
        "Capacity requirements planning",
        "Availability check for spare parts",
        "Mass change or mass editing"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following must a notification have?",
      "answer": "Reported by",
      "choices": [
        "Reported by",
        "Structuring of objects",
        "Availability check for spare parts",
        "Mass change or mass editing"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following must a notification have?",
      "answer": "Description",
      "choices": [
        "Description",
        "Time Confirmation",
        "Capacity requirements planning",
        "Availability check for spare parts"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following must a notification have?",
      "answer": "Notification data",
      "choices": [
        "Notification data",
        "Technical Completion Confirmation",
        "Structuring of objects",
        "Availability check for spare parts"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following must a notification have?",
      "answer": "Breakdown",
      "choices": [
        "Breakdown",
        "Printing work instruction papers",
        "Capacity requirements planning",
        "Availability check for spare parts"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following must a notification have?",
      "answer": "Damage location",
      "choices": [
        "Damage location",
        "Mass change or mass editing",
        "Capacity requirements planning",
        "Technical Completion Confirmation"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It normally triggers the order creation and order planning.",
      "answer": "Notifications",
      "choices": [
        "Notifications",
        "Maintenance Order Control Functions",
        "Implementation and Completion",
        "Bill of Material"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Order planning includes the steps to be performed, required parts, and any specialized tooling.",
      "answer": "This statement is TRUE.",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE.",
        "This statement is FALSE."
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "The maintenance orders can be created from maintenance plans, notifications, or made without any documents.",
      "answer": "This statement is TRUE.",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE.",
        "This statement is FALSE."
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Planned and unplanned materials are calculated based on internal activity rates and external service costs.",
      "answer": "This statement is FALSE.",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE.",
        "This statement is FALSE."
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which specifies the following statement?<BR>Control functions for maintenance orders can vary depending on the order type.",
      "answer": "Maintenance Order Control Functions",
      "choices": [
        "Maintenance Order Control Functions",
        "Planning",
        "Implementation and Completion",
        "Notification"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a function that a maintenance order provides?",
      "answer": "Mass change or mass editing",
      "choices": [
        "Mass change or mass editing",
        "Technical object",
        "Reported by",
        "Notification data"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a function that a maintenance order provides?",
      "answer": "Availability check for spare parts",
      "choices": [
        "Availability check for spare parts",
        "Time Confirmation",
        "Technical Completion Confirmation",
        "Technical Completion"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a function that a maintenance order provides?",
      "answer": "Capacity requirements planning",
      "choices": [
        "Capacity requirements planning",
        "Technical object",
        "Reported by",
        "Time Confirmation"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a function that a maintenance order provides?",
      "answer": "Printing work instruction papers",
      "choices": [
        "Printing work instruction papers",
        "Technical Completion Confirmation",
        "Reported by",
        "Notification data"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which specifies the following statements?<BR>A notification normally triggers the order creation and order planning. Order planning includes the steps to be performed, required parts, and any specialized tooling.",
      "answer": "Planning",
      "choices": [
        "Maintenance Order Control Functions",
        "Planning",
        "Implementation and Completion",
        "Notification"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which specifies the following statement?<BR>Planned and unplanned materials withdrawals, such as goods issues are possible.",
      "answer": "Implementation and Completion",
      "choices": [
        "Maintenance Order Control Functions",
        "Planning",
        "Implementation and Completion",
        "Notification"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a step of order completion?",
      "answer": "Time Confirmation",
      "choices": [
        "Time Confirmation",
        "Printing work instruction papers",
        "Capacity requirements planning",
        "Availability check for spare parts"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a step of order completion?",
      "answer": "Technical Completion Confirmation",
      "choices": [
        "Technical Completion Confirmation",
        "Damage location",
        "Notification data",
        "Location data"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a step of order completion?",
      "answer": "Technical Completion",
      "choices": [
        "Technical Completion",
        "Printing work instruction papers",
        "Capacity requirements planning",
        "Availability check for spare parts"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    }
  ]
}
